Imagine building your own team of
artificial intelligence agents [music] and having the power to give
them a set of skills, like in the
movie Matrix, when New starts
learning from Gu, simply by
uploading [music] that skill.
Unfortunately, it's not yet possible to do
this with human beings, but it's more
than possible to do it [make music] with
artificial intelligence.  And that's what
I'm going to show you in this video.  My name
is Rombraza, I am the founder and CEO of
Overlands, a nexialist creative school
where we connect creation,
business, and technology so you
can learn to realize your own ideas.
If you'd like to learn more
about Overl, be sure to check out the
link below in the description.  Let's
get to the video because we have
a lot to talk about today.  Imagine
building your own team of
artificial intelligence agents, defining a
hierarchy among them and, best of all,
being able to give each agent specific skills to
perform within their
role.  It's quite likely that you've already heard
of agents, maybe you've even tried to
create your own, but you didn't quite understand
how they worked.  Or perhaps
you've watched some of my recent
videos that I posted here on the channel
explaining how Cloud Code works,
how to install it, the main
differences, and the fundamentals of working on the
web, in the terminal, or in the application.  But
maybe you're still stuck, maybe
you're still waiting for the
right moment to build your agent.  Some
people might say that it's perhaps
too complicated or that it's something only
programmers and developers can handle.  But
actually, in this video, I'm going to
show you how you can still create
your own agents, your own
skills, and use them to your advantage
so they work together with you.   Okay, let's go
, I'll share
my screen with you here.  The first thing
I'm going to do is access the Cloud Code
Docs here.  As I've mentioned in other videos,
this is your workbook.  This is where you
can learn all about cloud code and reputable
companies that provide documentation.
So, Antropic has it, OpenI has it,
Google has it.  The difference is that most
people are too lazy to study, too
lazy to learn.  I know it
's different with you.  I'll
even leave the link to that document here for you.  Let's go
, because there's a lot of cool stuff
here.  The first thing I'm going to do
to make things easier is to come here to where it's in
English and change it to Brazilian Portuguese.  Okay,
now it's translated, easy to read, easy
to understand.  Now I'm going to go to the
side menu and click here on "
extend cloud code".  In this section, the
documentation explains how you can give
your cloud code more power.  And
down here we have a link to
skills, which I'll leave open, and
a link to subagents and agent teams,
which are the three things we're going to
talk about in this video.  To help you
understand as best as possible how
agents and
skills work, I need to explain this to you in
chronological order.  This way you will
understand when the need arose
for each of these resources to be
created.  So I'm going to pull out the
whiteboard here to explain better
how this works, and then we'll move on to the
practical creation of agents and
skills.  To summarize the story for
you, around 2022 we have
the arrival of GPT chat and then other
LLMs as well.  And we could use these
LLMs to build assistants.  I've even
explained what
assistants are in another video here on the
channel.  You can go there to
learn a little more.  But with
assistants, we started performing
specific tasks using
artificial intelligence.  Usually you send a
question, she answers, you ask for a text,
she delivers it, or even a
simple page, she delivers that too.  This has
evolved over time, hasn't it?  So, from
2022 until around 2024, we
used
artificial intelligence as assistants.  Openia
even created some
API connection processes for the assistants, because the
real power would come when the assistants
could call tools to
perform specific tasks, but
back then it didn't work so well, it
was complicated.  AI made more mistakes
until we get to 2024. In 2024,
Antropic, the owner of Cloud, launches MCP,
which is a protocol that allows you to
connect artificial intelligence with
other tools better than using
the API, using MCP itself.  This
was already a huge leap, an
important step here, because now it
was possible to use
artificial intelligence more efficiently to call
specific tools.  It was still
emerging there, things were just starting to
gain traction.  Once
artificial intelligences began
connecting with other programs and making
tool calls, we
officially entered the age of agents.
And here's where things start to get
interesting, because with the call of
tools,
artificial intelligences have gained arms and can
perform tasks for you.  That was the
main topic discussed in 2025.
A lot of progress happened there.  And at the
very end of 2025, these large
companies like Antropic, Google, and
Openi began launching their
code agents.  So put it here, code.
And 2026, or at least the beginning of it, right? The
moment I'm recording this video, it's
April.  In 2026, we're going to have
the boom of code agents.  When
code agents start to dominate the
market, then it's time to get into terminals,
into IDEs—if you don't know
what these concepts are, there's a link
below to a playlist where you can
learn all about it for free on
YouTube.  But when these
code agents start arriving, new challenges
arise as well.  In 2025, the main
idea was to use agents to
build entire teams.  So imagine
you have a specific agent of A
here.  Imagine this: this is my agent
A. And you give him instructions.
So, put it here as if it were a
playbook, a recipe, a step-by-step guide
for him on how to perform a
specific task.  More than that, you
also gave him an
identity, told him what
his role was, what he would be doing, and
what information he would have access to.
From there, we started building
teams of A-list agents and establishing a
hierarchy among them.  So, I have
a lead agent who delegates to the other
agents.  You'll see how to do that in this video,
too.  And each with
their own identity, each with
their own permissions.  This was
amazing and continues to be amazing and
very valuable, but it also has its
limitations.  Because think about it this way:
every time you open an
artificial intelligence to talk
to it, it has a context window,
and when it reaches a certain number of
tokens in a conversation, its performance starts to
decline.
This usually ranges between 60,000 and 100,000 tokens.
So, after this, the AI ​​will
continue working.  You'll see
many models that claim to have 1
million context windows.
They do have it, but there is a
performance decline.  This means that she
starts to have lower performance,
starts to hallucinate, starts to deliver
worse results, starts to spend more
tokens, and so on.  So what do
we start doing at this point?
Context window management.  So,
imagine that I hire an agent like that
to work with me.  We start
a conversation, we chat for a while, and at a
certain point,
his context window starts to get cluttered.  So what do
I need to do?  I need to open
a new window and continue the conversation.
However, there's a lot of
valuable information here that I don't want to lose,
that I want to store in a memory, or
at least that I want to better manage what
information the AI ​​has access to, so that
I always have a
clean, healthy window of context.
The problem is that when you start a
conversation with an agent from A,
the context window is already filled in.
And when you put a very
long instruction in it, that instruction also
fills up even more of the
context window.  And then there's just a little bit of
space left for you to actually talk
to her and ask her to do what
you want.  In other words, we already have here what
is called the system prompt, which is
a bit like the context prompt window.  Next
comes all your instruction here regarding the
procedure you want her to
perform.  And this is where things start to
get interesting.  Let's suppose you
want to use your AI agent to
build a house.  Beauty?  When he's
going to build that house, he needs to
go through a series of
different processes there, preparing materials,
preparing the foundation.  There are a number of
steps involved in building a house, right?
And you will give him
complete instructions on how to build this house from
start to finish.  So you write that
prompt-to-execute description of everything she needs to
do in there.  After you
create this entire instruction prompt,
you're going to bring in the entire instruction
from the beginning, from the moment
it prepares the batch.  After preparing the
plot of land, he lays the foundation, prepares the
materials, builds the walls, and so on. I'm
skipping steps here, but just so you
understand.  At a certain point, within
all of this instruction, you have an
instruction for him on how he is
going to prepare the cement mix.  Beauty?
Then he will prepare the
cement mix.  He needs sand, he
needs cement, he needs water.
And then you explain to him that first
he puts one in, then the other, then the
other, then mixes them, in short, there's a whole
process involved in making this cement.  But
this is inside a
giant prompt with several other steps as well.   So
every time your agent is going to
perform a task, let's say it's
already on the roof, it's not even
mixing cement anymore, it's building
the roof of the house.  However, as this is
in the instruction, every time this agent
runs, even if it's on the
roof, it will read step by step how
to prepare the
cement mix.  So he's there needing the
roof tiles, but he's
there.  First put the cement in, mix it
with sand, then add the water, and
mix again.  He's reading this all the time.  And
this is taking up space in your
context panel, even if you no
longer need that function or those
steps.  So here we have a
problem in managing all of this
instruction for the agent, because he has an
excess of instructions here.  You have
more information than he needs to do his
job.  This information is occupying
his context window.  But when
you actually go to use it to
perform the function, there's a little bit of the
context window left, which runs out quickly, and
it can't execute; it starts acting
erratically, and so on.  At this point,
we are creating the skills.
So Antropic, once again, created a
different way for you to manage this
context here.  So imagine you
have your agent, and your agent has
its instructions there, but you
only use a tiny bit of
its context window simply to tell
it where to find all the
information it needs.  For this purpose,
they created Cloud MD.  It's a file that
functions as an index.  After it
reads this Cloud MD and its System Prompt,
it can invoke some specific agent
with specific permissions to
work.  This will take up a
little more of the context window, but not as much
as before, because now you can
activate specific skills
at specific moments in the project.
So imagine there's a library,
let's put that library over here
.  And when this agent needs
a specific skill, for example,
preparing cement mix, he knows
that he has that skill at that moment.  He'll search through
all his skills here,
find the skill to prepare
cement mix, pull it into the context,
execute the skill, and move on.  In other
words, now I only pull out the
skill I need instead of
asking it to read all the skills all the
time.  This is the foundation
you need to understand in order to work with
the skills.  And now I'm going to show you in
practice how to do this, because it's
simpler than it seems.  Here in the
Cloud Code documentation, if you're looking to
extend Cloud Code, you'll find an
overview of the skills.  Here you have
all the instruction on how to work with
skills, going even more advanced than what
many people teach out there.  And I'm going to
show you how to do that in
practice now.  You can read the documentation here later
if you want to delve deeper,
okay?  Here in the documentation, it will
tell you to start the skills
by running a command in your terminal.
In our case here, I'm going to do it in an
even simpler way and I'll be developing
the process together with you.  So, the
easiest way to work with
skills is right here within your
Cloud Code application.  You'll probably
access the application on this page here.
You can come here to customize and here
you have skills.  When you click
on that little plus sign, you can explore
skills that Antropic itself
created, downloading those skills for
you.  Or you can also create your
own skills.  So I click
here on this little plus sign, create skill.
I can create this skill
by talking to Cloud, writing it
myself word for word, or doing the
padding.
The skills utilize a
file format called markdown.  It's a
very good format for working with AI, because
you can break the file into
different parts.  The important part
that we're going to see here in a moment is the
fronter, where you give a summary of
what's inside the file, so you don't
need to read the entire file to
understand if it's relevant to the
context in which you're working.
So, look how simple it is to create a
skill.  I can simply click here
to write the skill.  I'm going to give
this skill a name.  An example we can
give here is a skill focused
on, for example, understanding what ideas I have
, a briefing skill.  So,
I'm going to put here, look, briefing make, a
skill focused on creating briefings.
Here I will put the description of this
skill.  And it's very important that you
write this description accurately,
because the AI ​​will read the skill name first
, then the description.  If the
description shows the AI ​​that something is
relevant to the task, it reads the
entire skill.  If she sees in the description that it
's not what she needs, she doesn't read the rest
of the file.  Beauty?  So here you will
put the description.
There's even an example right here, look.  Generate
weekly status reports of
recent work.  Use when prompted for
updates or progress summaries.
So, if I'm going to
create a briefing, I can set it to
: generate a
complete briefing from the
user's instructions.  Use this when the
user has an idea that needs to be
developed.
No, I put a simple description here
.  And here in the instructions you can
put the step-by-step process of a framework, the
way you create your
briefings.  You write this here and it
will execute exactly step by step
as you put it.  So you're going to do
this first, then this,
then this, then this, and so on.
This is the simple way to create a
skill.  Later I'll show you how to
write the instruction here as well.
First, I want to show you the
tool.  What is important for you to
take into consideration here?  When you
create a skill directly in the application,
that skill goes to your user folder;
it doesn't go to the project folder
you're working on.  This is important
to mention because if you fill your
user folder with too many skills,
Cloud will need to read all the skills
to understand which ones it needs for each
project.  And often you'll
need different skills for
different projects.  So it doesn't make much
sense for you to carry
different skills to projects that
don't require those skills.  We
were talking about the example of the house.
Imagine you need to build a
house, and there's a skill that
teaches you how to make a
paper airplane.  You don't need that skill
to build a house, but it's
there in your user library,
and the cloud constantly needs to read
that information to know if it needs
that skill or not.  So here in the
user section, when you create a
skill in your global file, it's
important that you create skills that
will work for any type of
project.  These are generally skills
focused on project preparation, on
preparing the project's structure, which includes
which technologies and tools will be
used.  These are skills you use
frequently throughout the project, such as
committing and pushing,
which are processes where you upload
your project to the cloud, and versioning that
project.  So these are skills that
you will naturally use in
many different projects.  Now,
how do you go about developing
a specific skill for a
project you're working on?
To do this, you first need to create the
project, and within that project you will
work with the skills.  So,
let's see how this works.  It will
be easy for you.  We had already
created a Delta project here in one of the
last lessons on this channel.
Within this Delta project, there's this little
website that we created, and there's also
some documentation here.  If you want to
know more, I'll leave the link
below for you to watch this video.
I'll show you how we created this
in just a few minutes, okay?
What am I going to do?  Okay?  So, I'm here
in my work area.  I'm going to create a
new project here.  I'm going to call this project Project
Omega.  For each
video, I give the project a different name
.  Here's my folder.  I'm going to
open Antigravity.  If you want to
learn more about Antigravity, check out
our channel here.  There's a video where
I show you how to install it and how it
works.  With my antigravity software open, I'm
going to click here on "open folder" and
select that folder.  So, I'm here,
in the work area.  Project Omega,
select folder.  There aren't any files
in this folder yet, but we're going to
start working on it.  For that,
we need a specific context.
You will use agent skills when
creating a project.  Let's suppose
I'm going to create a study assistant here,
and then I need to create
some sub-agents: a
content explainer, an exercise generator, and an
answer evaluator later.  And they
need a set of skills,
for example, creating a quiz,
explaining a concept that has
different levels, or following a
specific learning framework.  So I'm going to
start this project here.  The first
step is to come here to the terminal.  If you
don't understand what's happening here
now, I recommend watching the other videos
first.  We have a playlist here that will
teach you how.  And now I'm
simply going to wake up the cloud within
the project, okay?  I'm going to press shift tab
here to enable
edit mode; it'll be easier to work with that way.  So here's
the thing: the first step is to
give the cloud some initial context so they
understand what the project is about.  I
can put it here, look, let's create a
study assistant where the user
learns a specific topic, like
nexalism, the future, etc.  And that's why we
need a structure.  So, the
structure basically consists of
subagents of... I'll put the
content explanation here.  Oops.
Content explainer, exercise generator.
Think about it, everyone here is an agent,
we'll talk more about this later.  An
evaluator of responses, and so on.
Beauty?  Okay, then.  We have
several agents here, each with a
specific identity and a
specific function.  And skills, skills
like, I'll put here, generating quizzes,
explaining a concept in levels, creating a
study plan, and that's it, okay?  So
that's the idea here, to keep it really simple so
you can see how these
agents are created.  So here, okay, how to create
an agent, studies, this is here,
we've already explained to him what
I'm going to talk about.  Create a briefing
detailing the project idea.  I like
to start like this, don't you?  You can even, if
you want, run a plan mode on it
here too, and it will plan
the idea here.  The play mode takes a little
longer to set up, but it's worth it, it pays off,
but for this video I'm just going to ask
him to generate a briefing for us.  Then
he'll understand what our idea is,
write a briefing, and save that
briefing in our folder here.
So all we have to do is wait for him to do
it.  While Clou works on
our briefing, I want to introduce you to
our community.  You've always sought a
place where you could evolve,
continue learning from people who
want to help you achieve results, people who
are on the same journey as you,
building projects, realizing their
own ideas.  I want to introduce you
to Overl and also Vanguarda.  Overl is
our ecosystem as a whole.  There
you can learn in any way you
want.  If you want to watch a class, read
a text, or listen to a lecture, you
can do that within our
ecosystem. You'll have access to various
materials, book recommendations, and classes
to watch. But there's also
Vanguarda, which is our
results acceleration program for those who want to
build a business within the
creative economy.  If you want to realize your ideas and
create your own tools, it's great to
learn about the cutting edge.  It's one
thing to study alone and
learn a skill, but it's quite another to
learn from someone who is already on
the path you want to follow.
Sooner or later you'll realize, if you have
n't already, that the secret isn't
in learning to click buttons or follow
tutorials, but in having good ideas and
turning those ideas into reality.
How do you know if what you're
creating is actually useful?  Does it make a
difference in people's lives?  How
can you validate your ideas?  That's what
we do at the forefront.  The
vanguard is a collective program; it's a
program that includes in-person meetings,
a program that meets every
week.  I can tell you that there's
nothing quite like the avant-garde.  And right now
I just want you to know,
I'm just introducing you so you know
that this exists and that we're here
ready to welcome you when the
time is right, okay?  Then check it out
a little more.  I'll leave the link
below as well, in case you're interested.
And we're going back because I think
Cloud is finished.  Look how
interesting.  So he finished
writing the briefing for us here.  He
even mentioned which points are
worth deciding before he begins.
This is information that I didn't give him,
and he's asking me how we're
going to work with it.  Since my
goal here is mainly to show you the agents and
skills, I won't go into detail about
that part here.  The point is that we
have the entire briefing right here above.  Look at
the file he created.  He even
explained here how the
agent architecture will work.  So there is a
main orchestrating agent, a
content explanation agent, an
exercise generator, and an
answer evaluator.  They are three different agents,
right?  Four, actually.  And they also
have the skills here, look,
summonable skills, hierarchies, explaining levels,
study plan.  What am I going to do
here now?  The first step, okay?  This might
not be the best possible step, maybe
you could do better with the
skills here, but I want to show you the
simplest way so you can see that you can
start today.  What I can do here
is ask the AI ​​itself to create the agents and
skills for me.  I'll
improve them later.  I'm going to do this
because Cloud will create the
entire structure here, and you'll see how it
works.  The first thing I'm going to
do is press the clear bar to clear
my context window so I can
continue communicating with the cloud.  Since
we already have this briefing here,
I can now give a slash init.  When I
do this, the cloud will create the
cloud.md file, where it will write the
index of this project.  Even though there's only
one briefing file now, he
can already understand the context and
the structure we'll be
working with.  So we run the
barrait here to create the cloud.  MD.
Here he's already saying, look, that the
repository is empty, that's correct according to the
briefing.  MD, which doesn't have any code yet,
doesn't have any packages and doesn't have any
structure for it to understand where
the folders and files are located.  Then he says he's
going to write the Cloud MD focused on the
architecture that's written in the
briefing, but later we can also
refine this file here,
okay?  I'm just creating this so you can see
how the structure will work.
So, the file is right here.
Hey, cool, he created this file for
us.  You'll see that the file has a
status, it has project architecture, it's
already showing the layout, that there
will be a file, a folder called cloud.
Within this cloud folder, we will have the
agents and the skills.  In addition,
here is also the content that he will
save inside another folder.
Beauty?  Once we've done this
, I can press clear again,
and now I'm going to ask him to create
the agents and skills for us.  I
can either type `slash agents` here and it
will tell me, "Look, running
agents, create a new agent."  Here, he
also has the plugins that I have
installed within this user account, but
we're not going to do it that way, okay?
I could do it manually here.  I'm going to
give an ES.  I'm going to tell him in
natural language that I want him to
create all the agents and all the skills.
But now comes an important part.  Look what
I'm going to do now.  Create the
agents and skills needed for
this project.
Do it.  Just turn the Caps Lock down a bit
.  Do this in parallel.  What does this
mean?  He's not going to execute the
creation of all these agent skills
in this window here, in this chat
we're having.  To help you understand
this a little better, imagine
this: imagine we have cloud
code here.  And Cloud Code is
chatting with us here in this chat.
So, there's a little chat here and we
're in it.  Beauty?  We're working together with
Cloud Code.  There's a conversation going on here.
What will he do when you tell
him to work in parallel?  He
will invoke other cloud codes.  And these
cloud codes here, each one will have its
own window; they won't appear in
our conversation, okay?  It will actually
give you information that they
are working, but each of them will
work in their own context window,
executing what you
asked them to do.  So, what do
we want to do here?  We want, we
're asking this person to do the
following: you're going to be the leader,
and you're going to ask each of these people
here for a part of this project, and each of
them will create it.  So you're going to create
agent one, you're going to create agent two,
you're going to create agent three, and so on
.  This is good because it preserves
its context window and puts a brand
new, zero-mileage cloud here
to create only this
specific task.  So he's well-
focused on what he needs to
create.  You could have dozens of them
created by you here, okay?  So take a look at
how this happens in practice.  We
'll talk to him here.  Do this
in parallel.  You don't execute, you
only delegate.  Okay, you'll see what's
going to happen here now.  He's going to
start calling each of the agents.
The agent he's calling is the
Cloud Code Crew itself, okay?  He is not
a subagent.  And this is something
important for you to understand.  Cloud
Code, by itself, is already an
artificial intelligence code agent.  When you
create your own agents,
Antropic calls them subagents.  It is
their agents there that the Cloud can
invoke for a given task.
Beauty?  So, look what he's
saying here.  I will delegate the creation
of the six files, which are three
sub-agents and three skills, in parallel.
Each agent will read the briefing and the cloud
MD for context and write the
specific file.  Now, what's going to start
happening?  Look, it's initializing
the first agent, which is the agent that
will create the content explainer sub-agent
.  Now he's going to initialize the
others.  Look, I'm going to let him
do this here, and he's going to start, look, he
created the cloud folder, he's going to start
running the other agents here together in
parallel.  So, look, two
agents are rotating.  Right now we have one person
creating the content explainer and another
creating the
exercise generator.  Every time he asks me for this
, he's asking for
permission to create new folders.
So, he created the "agents" folder here and
is working inside that folder.
It's running two now, it's about to
load the third one here too.  Look, there are
three agents patrolling right now.  The
response evaluator as well.  The idea here is that these
are raw clouds, okay?  These are raw clouds
that are creating sub-agents that will
work on those
specific tasks.  Here, he's just asking me for
permission to create the files and
folders.  So he created the first
agent here, the content explainer.
I'll open it for
you in a little while.  Let me just close this tab
here.  What you need to see now is that
we have a cloud folder.  Inside this
Cloud folder, we have an agents folder.
And within that "agents" folder, we have the
content explainer.  Now he's
asking me for permission to create the
skills folder.  Now we have two folders
here, look, the agents folder and the
skills folder.  The first one is already inside the agents folder;
the others are being created.
Look, one here has already been done, look,
Don.  The others are still being made,
you see?  But I have several agents
working in parallel.  I'll give you a
yes right now.
Leave them loading here, and the skill
is being created as well.  So, each
skill has its own folder.  This is
important information when we
talk about the folder architecture here in the
cloud: when you create an agent,
you just need to create this "point cloud" folder,
then inside the "points" folder.
And inside that "agents" folder, you're going to
put the MD (Medical Domain) of your agent, which
we'll see now.  However, when you
work with skills, the architecture is
different.  You have a folder called "skills," which
needs to be inside the "cloud" folder.
Then you have your skill folder.
So, each skill has its own folder.  And
inside that folder there's a file
called skill.m.
This file has the same name in
all folders, but the way to
identify it is by the folder name.  That's how
the AI ​​will identify it, okay?
So she's creating it here while I'm
explaining it to you.  Look, two agents have already
been created, one of which was the
content explainer.  Let's see here, close
all the tabs, see.  We have the
answer evaluator, the
content explainer, and the exercise generator.  And
he's still developing the skills.  So,
we have the skill of explaining in levels,
the skill of generating quizzes, and the skill of creating
study plans.  Beauty?  I can create
as many skills as I want, but here I
'm creating the skills directly within the
project I'll be working on.  If I
come here inside the agent, we have
here the entire skill file
that he created.  Beauty?  And what is
important for you to understand here?
This information is also available here in the
cloud code documentation.  Just look.
So you're going to access Cloud Code, go
here to extend cloud code, then scroll
down here to skills.  Within the
skills section, if you scroll down here, you
'll find an explanation of how to
write a skill.  Then he's going to
show you the path that was just
created there, and he's showing
you a structure for writing this in
MarkD.  Then you can test where they
live, so which files, in which
folders they are located, right,
their directory, depending on the level
you're putting this skill at.  So,
when it's an enterprise skill, it's something the
whole company can use; it's
centralized in one place.  If it's a personal file,
it will be located in your user folder.
When it's at the project level, it
will be located inside the "cloud" folder within the
project.  And when it's a plugin, it will be
located inside the plugin's folder.  If you
scroll down a bit further here, you'll find the entire
folder structure, and further down
, you'll find the configuration options.  So,
there are different types of skill content.
Below is a small table, take a look, with
the fields.  It has a name (which is not
mandatory), a description, and information on when you will
use it.  There's a lot of
information you can put here
to quickly read that information
simply by pressing true or false.  We
call this the Boolean model.  You say
yes or no.  So, for example,
we have here, look, disable model
invocation.  What does that mean?  If
you set this to true, it means
that the cloud will not
automatically load this skill; it will only use
this skill when you request it.  This is
useful for managing
its context window, as I've already explained to you.
So here's the model she's going to
use, what tools are
available, the context, the agents, and
also her level of effort, whether she
'll spend more time thinking or not.
The hooks, which I already explained in another
lesson here, are also explained on the channel
, you know?  Here you can
simply define with yes and no what
Cloud can or cannot do with this
skill.  And where is that located?  This is located in the
field that we call the front.   I'm
going to show you what a
frontter is.  In this case, I was showing
the agent; I'll go to the agents too,
but let's understand the skill here.  So the
skill is inside the folder.  This is the
skill to explain in levels.  If I look at
the file here, you'll see that I
have three little lines.  Then, within
those three little lines, I have some
information, and then I have three little
lines again.  What lies between
those three little lines is what's called
the front.
This is the most important information for Cloud to
read the skill and understand whether or not it will
use it.  In this case, when
Cloud creates the skill for you, it creates
it in a very basic way.  He
only put the name and
description here, but I could
add more information, for
example, allowed tools.
And then I put two points here and
write which tools he can or
cannot use.  It's available right here
.  Allowed Tools.  So, I define for him
what he can and cannot
do in terms of tools.  And I
can include various other pieces of
information about them here.  All of these
I can set, for example, if
I don't want this model to be
used, I set it like this, true.
Ready.  Now it will only activate here
for me.  Hey, show up!  He will only
activate that skill for me if I ask
him to activate it.  It won't activate
automatically.  I can put here, for
example, what the model is.  So, I come
here, write modelis pontos and say, for
example, that I want the opus here.  And so it
goes.  Here you define the front end,
and from there you can better manage
when, how, and through which this skill will be
used.  To give you an example
, look, there are several examples here
.  Let me load one here.  For
example, I have a front-end that's
disabling the invocation of the
model here.  This means he will only use
that skill if you ask him to
use it.  If I leave it here, there are other
examples.  Look, tools enabled.
Then he wrote here what AI can and cannot
do in terms of tools, and so on
.  Here he will give
you several examples.  Here I have
another front end showing which agent
uses this skill.  That's a
cool thing too.  You can create an agent,
and only that specific agent, when
activated, will activate this skill
.  No other agent can use
this skill here, and so on, okay?  Here
are several examples; I recommend you take
a look at them later. But once you've
defined the front-end, here comes the full
explanation of your skill, which you'll
write in natural language.  I
recommend you ask it to write
the skill once and then read it as the AI
wrote it here.  This will give you the
framework for how you can do it
too.  But basically, here's the step-by-
step process.  Look, first do this, then
this, then this, then this, and so on
, okay?  This will depend a
lot on your background and which
frameworks you are already familiar with.  If you already
have a structure, a step-by-step process, a
method for performing a
specific task, you can ask AI for that
.  If you don't have one, you can ask her
to make one for you too, okay?
So this here is a skill.  Let's see
how it works inside the agent.  So,
we have this first part here, which is
very important, which is the front.  Three
little lines on top, three little lines
on the bottom.  Everything in here is what
the AI ​​will read first before reading everything
else.  It's for her to understand whether
or not she needs this right now, what the
possibilities are within this context.  So, in this
case, we have a name, description, and
tools available for this
subagent.  To help you understand this
a little better, I'll refer you to the
Cloud Code documentation.  I'm here to
extend Cloud Code, and below
I have subagents.  If you go here, you'll
find a full explanation of how to use
subagents.  And down here, look how
cool, he's going to show us what
the structure of the front panel is.  Look
here.  So here are
supported frontend fields.  Then comes the name,
description, tools,
disabled tools, model, mode, and the types of
permissions that we'll have.
Maximum number of turns, skills, and so on
, right?  Connectors, hooks.
I've already explained to you what these are.
Here you can simply connect.  And it
's easier than it looks, okay?  Because
basically you can get the
information you need.  In this
case, our AI only created the name,
description, and tools, but I could,
for example, put the following here.
Look, I'm going to start a new thread here, and I want to
say which model he's going to use.
So I'll give it a colon and I'll write it
here.  No, in this one I want to use the
son.  All done.  Now he will load
this model.  Every time he uses
that agent.  I can also tell him the
following.  Look, permission mode.
I can copy this, add a colon, and
then I'll enable a type of
permission.  He'll tell me what they are.
I have def, accept permission,
automatic, don't ask, and bypass or
schedule.  Let's assume this is a
planning agent.  He is the
evaluator of responses.  So I'll just
put here that only edits can be accepted.
All done.  I'm moving on to the next one.  I want
him to use a specific skill.  So
I'll put it here, see, skills.  And then the
answer evaluator will use the study plan here
.  Let's put, for example,
I'll put a study plan here.  And
now he can use that skill, and so on
.  So here you'll put what
he can't do, permissions.  And
this has to be really short,
straight to the point, because you're going to read this
fronter first.  If she sees that it's what
she needs, then she'll read the
rest.  Below is a description of
what this subagent is.  The AI ​​itself created
this description for us.  This is not the
most optimized way to create a subagent.  It's
always good to read and understand if it's
working the way you want.
But to start, so you understand the
structure, here it is, it's a good way to
understand how it works.  The
AI ​​itself created an agent here for you,
okay?  So, I'm going to give it a try here to
save it.  Whenever you see that little ball, press
Ctrl+S. And now you understand
how agents and
skills work.  I showed you both of them
here, their structure.  From
now on, how does it work?  If
you want to call upon these agents or
skills in a project, let's take a
look at that.  I'm going to close this
now.  The entire project is already here.  Look,
our agents worked here
in parallel and created all the
files.  Here he's just explaining to me
everything he created.  So, let's take a
look at the folder structure here.  We
have the briefing that we created at the beginning
of the project, the cloud.md file, and we have the
cloud folder.  Inside the cloud folder we
have the agents folder.  Here we have
three agents.  And within the skills folder,
we also have skills here.  with three
different skills.  The structure is a
little different.  Within agents,
it loads the MD directly; within skills, it
loads the folder, and within the folder, there's the
skill.  The name is always the same, you
see?  Look, skill MD, skill MD, skill
MD, but Cloud can identify
which skill it is by its folder name.
Beauty?  Now, look how interesting.  I
can close this now.  Here we have
our terminal.  Or maybe there was a little bug here,
which sometimes happens.  Look, I'm going to
load it here.  Or I'll give a clear slash.   There's
an option here, and then I reset the
project to continue, or I can open
a new one here as well.  Whatever you
think is best, is fine, because sometimes the cloud is
having this bug, you see?  So, I
have a bit of OCD, I open a new
cloud here, look.  So, let us load it
here for us.  I'll use shift-tab
to enable edit mode here,
easy.  And now look how interesting, if
I type "skills" here and press
enter, you'll see that down here I
have three ONS skills.  The ones
with the padlock here are skills that are
installed directly on my user account, which is why
they're locked like that. They
're enabled, but to
manage them, I need to go to the
user folder or my
Cloud application, where I can manage the
skills as well.  But in this case, look,
these three appeared here, which are the
project-level skills.  I'll give you an
ES here.  If I type "agents" here now,
type "agents" here, you'll also see it
loading, look at the library.  And here I
have project agents: the
response evaluator, the content explainer, and the
exercise generator.  There are three agents
I can work with here.  Now that
you understand how the folder structure works
, what subagents are, what
skills are, how to create them,
how to edit them, and what a fronter is, you
're probably thinking: "Juan, that's
great, but I freeze up. I don't know
what to write in the file, I don't know
where to start, I don't know if what I
'm doing is valid. Are you
wasting tokens, creating solutions
that you won't even use yourself? Will
what you're doing really
help you achieve better results,
improve your life, or help other
people?" If you want to answer these
questions and truly want to use
artificial intelligence to build
relevant projects, then I want to
tell you about Atlas. It will be a
whole weekend where I will build
a complete brand system,
an entire project using
artificial intelligence agents and skills, right in front of you. I wo
n't be teaching you theory at this
event. I will build it in front of you, and
you will be able to build it along with me. And
as if seeing me create it right there in front of you was
n't enough, you will also have
access to a series of materials and will be
able to learn about our...  Community, see
other people who are creating
projects just like you. We
even interviewed some of them,
and we're going to share their stories so
you can watch and understand everything that's
possible with all these
technologies. If you don't want to miss
this, I highly recommend you click
the link below and
buy your ticket, because it's really
very cheap. It's worth clicking
just to see the price, it will impress you,
and you'll get two whole days creating a
project together. To not miss out, click the
link here. If this video was helpful to
you, if I managed to answer your
question, if you understood a little
better how to create agents, how to create
skills, comment below so I
know. Like this video too so I
know you're enjoying it and
YouTube shows it to more people.
And check if you're not already following
our channel, follow us, because now I'm
bringing you a series of powerful videos
. And speaking of
video series, if you haven't yet watched how to
install Cloud Code, what the
fundamentals of Cloud Code are, how to connect
Cloud Code with Antigy, check them out.
Within our channel, because it's an
entire playlist, it's practically a
free course here for you to learn
how to use the cloud. There are people who
charge a lot to teach what I'm
teaching you here. So, take advantage,
it's right in front of you now, it's available
here. You just have to want to learn,
okay? So I'll leave it at that,
I hope you enjoyed this
video and I'll see you in the next one. See you later
and bye.